- Projects
  - [Project name], [Date normalized]
    [Primary archt/firm][1]
    [Primary archt/firm][2]
    [Client]
    [Collaborators][1][Name]
    [Collaborators][2][Name]
    [FAST Geographic]; [Place name]
    City: [City]
    County: [County]
    State/Province: [State/Province]
    Country: [Country]
    Street address: [Street address]
    Street address (normalized): [Street address normalized]
    Coordinates (EPSG:4326): [coordinates]
    Project Number: [Project number]
    Number of items: [Number of items]
    Contributor notes: [Contributor notes]
    Notes: [Notes]
    Accession #: [Accession #]
    Processing completion date: [Processing completion date]
    Processor: [Processor]
    Entry date: [Entry date]
    Rev. date: [Rev. date]
    AAA Projects Database Unique ID: [unique ID]
    - [Material types][1], [Date normalized]
      [AAA box #] [AAA folder #] [AAA roll #]
      [Material types][1]; [Material types][2]; [Set types][1]; [Set types][2]; [Media][1]; [Media][2]
      Date on drawings: [Date on drawings]
      Pres. notes: [Pres. notes]
      Treatment completed A: [treatment completed A]
      Treatment completed B: [treatment completed B]
      Treatment completed C: [treatment completed C]
      Treatment completed D: [treatment completed D]
      Treatment completed E: [treatment completed E]
    - [Material types][2], [Date normalized]
    - [Material types][3], [Date normalized]
- Projects
  - St. Paul’s Evangelical Lutheran Church. First unit., 1957
    J. Eugene Wukasch
    Robert L. Miller
    St. Paul’s Evangelical Lutheran Church
    Louisiana--Lake Charles; St. Paul’s Evangelical Lutheran Church
    City: Lake Charles
    County: Calcasieu
    State/Province: Louisiana
    Country: United States
    Street address: Brien Lake Road
    Street address (normalized): 1620 E Prien Lake Rd, Lake Charles, LA 70601
    Coordinates (EPSG:4326): 30.197629661598036,-93.19714747795992
    Project Number: 5701
    Number of items: 75
    Notes: Presentation drawing on board (1 item)
    Accession #: 2001008
    Processor: BHN; kap
    Entry date: Fri Mar 14 2003
    Rev. date: Fri Oct 21 2011
    AAA Projects Database Unique ID: 6646
    - Drawings, 1957
      WUK dr.1 WUKr155.01; WUKr155.02
      architectural drawings (visual works); specifications; structural drawings; mechanical drawings (building systems drawings); interior views; electrical plans; presentation drawings (proposals); reprographic copies; mounting board; tracing paper; Paper; tracing cloth
      Date on drawings: 1957
      Pres. notes: E fasteners/rehouse
      Treatment completed E: y
    - Specifications, 1957
  - Maranatha Temple Christian Center, 1982-1983
    Maranatha Temple Christian Center
    Texas--Mont Belvieu; Maranatha Temple Christian Center
    City: Mont Belvieu
    County: Chambers
    State/Province: Texas
    Street address: Highway 146 off Interstate 10
    Street address (normalized): 12319 N Hwy 146, Mont Belvieu, TX 77535
    Coordinates (EPSG:4326): 29.8630395,-94.8949790
    Project Number: 8125
    Number of items: 44
    Notes: Mounted presentation drawings on board (2 items, interior and exterior)
    Processor: BHN; djc
    Entry date: 2003-03-14
    Rev. date: 2011-01-24
    AAA Projects Database Unique ID: 6647
    - Drawings, 1982-1983
      WUK dr.1 WUKr156
      architectural drawings (visual works); specifications; project files; architectural drawings (visual works); structural drawings; site plans; presentation drawings (proposals); design drawings; interior views; Paper; reprographic copies
      Date on drawings: 1982-1983
    - Specifications, 1982-1983
    - Job files, 1982-1983